Yes, my strongest abandoned bird is
Janko's potassium water mixed with manuka honey
Mom's special drink!
Here is my best bird to throw away!
Aronamin C and Yakult for Oroyaku!
It's a classic, isn't it?
It's a classic!
I'll let you do it. Hey...
It's sort of time.
ran
E dette nabe masu masu!
E dette pot, please.
Will you eat it?
Yes, so here is my best steady!
Yes! Stambur!
But I've been mixing it.
After I'm done with the customization...
Stop being so subtle!
If you find this video interesting, please click the like button and subscribe to my channel!
Pretty for you Rin to hirose Medetai my life
I want to make it come true with you, let's hope
By the way, Starbucks, what's that?
I tried it for the first time.
Drip coffee with caramel syrup
caramel sauce added milk added caramel sauce added milk added caramel sauce added milk added caramel sauce added milk added caramel sauce added milk
It looks really good, doesn't it?
It's like a latte.
Looks delicious!
That looks delicious!
I've decided to have it!
I want to drink it normally.
Yes, I do.
Bye-bye.
I don't know, but it's so smooth, it's like freeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeezing,
It's like the words come out so smoothly, don't you think?
Sure.
I'd like to make it a sketching song.
But I'm not a smooth singer, I only rap.
Really? Really?
But do you have lines?
Lines!
Yes, I have lines.
There's a special one, isn't there?
I don't think so.
Then, I had them take it.
I wonder what it is.
Music, please!
It's okay, you know, I haven't had a sip yet.
I'm out of that music without even saying three bottles.
It's delicious.
I opened my palm.
I felt warmth a few times.
I looked at that man.
Where the hell did he go?
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm here.
I've been waiting for you.
I'll see you in Shinagawa on December 22nd.
Oh!
Bravo!
That's great!
If I can do it, then anyone who drinks this can do it.
What? What about Moeka?
I can't drink black.
Then I'll have to give it to her.
I'll have coffee.
I don't drink black.
Please! Mr. Kanayama!
I'll just drink some and see if I can get Ryder in the mood.
Okay, Mr. Kanayama!
Let's have an impromptu over-the-rainbow challenge!
Go ahead!
I don't have anything.
This one's a little big.
Very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very...
This is where I am.
Oh, yeah.
There it is.
Oh, my God
Here the sea and the sky everything is blue
Blue even from my member
This is
My earth
I say it like Another Sky.
Oh, no!
Dominance!
This is awkward.
Can I get one more?
No, I don't know.
It was kind of funny.
It's terrible, isn't it?
Whenever I slip.
I'm never the last one to slip.
I'm not going to assume that I'm slipping.
I'm not slipping.
Okay, Yukimayuka.
impromptu over-the-rainbow challenge!
Go ahead!
On stage
This song has the best voice
What's this?
Delicious!
Caramel syrup, light ice cream, caramel-topped coffee.
Oh, my God.
It's coming, it's still coming
It's coming down, it's coming down
Feel the feeling
what should I do?
I'm really fucked.
I couldn't do it
I feel like I'm going to end up at the end
Please drink.
Wait a minute.
This is really awkward.
So... we've talked a lot about stay-drinking.
We've talked about it a lot.
I've been thinking...
There's a stage drink, right?
I don't want stage food.
I know what you mean.
I can't help it if I'm MCing.
I don't know why the MC is thinking about fried food during the MC.
I'm thinking about food.
I put it in the corner of my mind.
I want to eat it while I'm MCing.
That's the only time.
He leaves it to others to think about it.
No way.
That's why...
It's the same with the stay-drinks.
When we're on stage...
I've asked everyone to prepare something they'd like to eat
I asked everyone to prepare something they'd like to eat.
Stay drinks.
Let me give you an example.
Every time I prepare something, I prepare it at home.
That's home, isn't it?
Here are my stay-drinks.
Ta-da!
I want to eat!
Pork and kimuchi nabe.
Can you eat this?
It's not very hot, but...
But when we eat it on stage, I thought it would be better if it wasn't hot.
I thought this is just right.
I want to eat it.
Can you eat it?
You're in the middle of dancing, right?
Yes, I can.
We're singing and dancing in the middle of a performance.
Can you do that?
Because I'm not allowed to sing in many places.
That's not true.
So you're not coming over there because I'm self-deprecating?
I don't think so.
No, it's not true.
I can't eat that.
Can you guys, like, eat during a fryout?
I don't think so.
We sing a little bit here and there.
I don't have any more after 2A.
Can you guys eat gradients?
There are a few gradations here and there.
I won't have it until after the second chorus.
I won't be back until the end of the 2nd chorus.
Can we all eat at Love is Love?
I want some Momo.
I'm not in 2A, so I can eat all the time.
It's healthy to eat during the show.
And there's soup, so it'll keep your throat moist.
It's spicy. It's supposed to be for your throat.
No, no, no.
I want it to taste good.
I see.
It's like hot pork.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's alcohol.
And it burns fat.
Five birds with one stone.
That's great.
Well, I'll just have a bite to start.
A tasting.
Oh, yes.
Looks delicious.
It looks really good.
I'm going to have a lot of it!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Yes, it's delicious!
Okay, so I'd like you to try it right away.
I'd like everyone to take their first position for a moment and do a little gradation.
I'm going to dance it right.
I'm going to dance really well. I can't really feel it.
I've never even told you it's a white bath.
That's right.
I can feel it.
To Nisabi
To Nisabi-Barry, to Blue Blaze.
Yes, okay.
Okay, gradient music start.
Oh, nice.
Pickle in black and white.
Are you still there?
Are you still here?
You're gonna have to work with me here.
Give me your hand.
You're gonna get caught!
They're gonna know. They're gonna know.
Is that too much?
There's a guy here who's a fake.
You can't afford to be.
I can't afford it.
He's coming.
Can't you just fly away?
It's coming.
I'll sing.
Yes, sir.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not working.
I can't sing.
I cover my mouth while I sing.
That's a total no-no!
He's gone.
That's a definite no-no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
There's more of them.
Don't make me laugh.
I know you can do it.
We're all dancing together.
Cute Yuka!
Let's dance together
It's not fair
No fair!
Very petite
that makes you want to hug her
Oh, yes, yes
Laughing
a name for laughter
full of tone
small addition